Marted streets riddled with bodies that sway Lost in a haze, but they're not far away Eyes glazed open, memories erased Standing in silence, stuck in disgrace Frostbitten fingers gripping empty dreams Reality buries them under routine
Statues on the side while gay don't move or tweak.
Frozen in the moment, caught on the break.
Time's moving past them, but they're stuck in place.
Concrete confession on every wasted face.
Oh, oh, stand so still.
Oh, chills and brilf.
Sirens pass by, but nobody stirs.
Needles in hand and not being deters.
Dreams broken down where the pavement's cracked.
Shadows alive, but hope is what they lack.
Sunrise, it's eyes that never see.
Trapped in a loop on Ellis Street.
Statues on the side, but they don't move or break.
Frozen in the moment, caught on the brink.
Time's looming past them, but they're stuck in place.
Concrete confession on every waste bit base.
Oh, oh, stand so still.
Oh, chills and pain.